[
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0204_0101_UndyingAppetite",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0204_0101_d_00_Container_UndyingAppetite",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0210_Barkeep",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_08",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0204_0101_UndyingAppetite_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0204_0101_UndyingAppetite_title",
        "Description": "@0204_0101_UndyingAppetite_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0204_0101_UndyingAppetite_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0204_0101_UndyingAppetite_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0204_0101_UndyingAppetite_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0204_0101_UndyingAppetite_complete",
        "QuestArcTag": "BrightwoodArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0202_0101_BlindingLight",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0202_0101_d_00_Container_BlindingLight",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0202_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_01",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0202_0101_BlindingLight_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0202_0101_BlindingLight_title",
        "Description": "@0202_0101_BlindingLight_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0202_0101_BlindingLight_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0202_0101_BlindingLight_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0202_0101_BlindingLight_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0202_0101_BlindingLight_complete",
        "QuestArcTag": "BrightwoodArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0202_0102_PreacherJohannes",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0202_0102_d_00_Container_PreacherJohannes",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0202_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_02",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "02_Quest_01",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0202_0102_PreacherJohannes_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0202_0102_PreacherJohannes_title",
        "Description": "@0202_0102_PreacherJohannes_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0202_0102_PreacherJohannes_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0202_0102_PreacherJohannes_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0202_0102_PreacherJohannes_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0202_0102_PreacherJohannes_complete",
        "QuestArcTag": "BrightwoodArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0210_0101_UnholyGreenThumb",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0210_0101_d_00_Container_UnholyGreenThumb",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0204_Overseer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_06",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "02_Quest_08",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0210_0101_UnholyGreenThumb_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0210_0101_UnholyGreenThumb_title",
        "Description": "@0210_0101_UnholyGreenThumb_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0210_0101_UnholyGreenThumb_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0210_0101_UnholyGreenThumb_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0210_0101_UnholyGreenThumb_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0210_0101_UnholyGreenThumb_complete",
        "QuestArcTag": "BrightwoodArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0202_0103_HeldBelowtheSurface",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0202_0103_d_00_Container_HeldBelowtheSurface",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0202_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_03",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "02_Quest_02",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0202_0103_HeldBelowtheSurface_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0202_0104_HeldBelowtheSurface_title",
        "Description": "@0202_0103_HeldBelowtheSurface_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0202_0103_HeldBelowtheSurface_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0202_0103_HeldBelowtheSurface_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0202_0103_HeldBelowtheSurface_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0202_0103_HeldBelowtheSurface_complete",
        "QuestArcTag": "BrightwoodArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0203_0101_PocketfulofMemories",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0203_0101_d_00_Container_PocketfulofMemories",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0203_Survivalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_04",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "02_Quest_03",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0203_0101_PocketfulofMemories_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0203_0101_PocketfulofMemories_title",
        "Description": "@0203_0101_PocketfulofMemories_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0203_0101_PocketfulofMemories_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0203_0101_PocketfulofMemories_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0203_0101_PocketfulofMemories_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0203_0101_PocketfulofMemories_complete",
        "QuestArcTag": "BrightwoodArc2"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0203_0102_AncientProblemsAncientSolutions",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0203_0102_d_00_Container_AncientProblemsAncientSolutions",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0202_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_05",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "02_Quest_04",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0203_0102_AncientProblemsAncientSolutions_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0203_0103_AncientProblemsAncientSolutions_title",
        "Description": "@0203_0102_AncientProblemsAncientSolutions_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0203_0102_AncientProblemsAncientSolutions_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0203_0102_AncientProblemsAncientSolutions_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0203_0102_AncientProblemsAncientSolutions_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0203_0102_AncientProblemsAncientSolutions_complete",
        "QuestArcTag": "BrightwoodArc2"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0205_0101_RuinousLabor",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0205_0101_d_00_Container_RuinousLabor",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0205_Artificer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_07",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "02_Quest_03",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0205_0101_RuinousLabor_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0205_0101_RuinousLabor_title",
        "Description": "@0205_0101_RuinousLabor_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0205_0101_RuinousLabor_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0205_0101_RuinousLabor_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0205_0101_RuinousLabor_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0205_0101_RuinousLabor_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0204_0102_OfOurOwnFleshandBlood",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0204_0102_d_00_Container_OfOurOwnFleshandBlood",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0204_Overseer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_09",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "02_Quest_04",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0204_0102_OfOurOwnFleshandBlood_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0204_0102_OfOurOwnFleshandBlood_title",
        "Description": "@0204_0102_OfOurOwnFleshandBlood_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0204_0102_OfOurOwnFleshandBlood_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0204_0102_OfOurOwnFleshandBlood_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0204_0102_OfOurOwnFleshandBlood_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0204_0102_OfOurOwnFleshandBlood_complete",
        "QuestArcTag": "BrightwoodArc3"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0204_0103_IsleofMadness",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0204_0103_d_00_Container_IsleofMadness",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0204_Overseer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_10",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "02_Quest_09",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0204_0103_IsleofMadness_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0204_0103_IsleofMadness_title",
        "Description": "@0204_0103_IsleofMadness_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0204_0103_IsleofMadness_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0204_0103_IsleofMadness_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0204_0103_IsleofMadness_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0204_0103_IsleofMadness_complete",
        "QuestArcTag": "BrightwoodArc3"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0202_0104_Weavers_Vector",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 30,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0202_0104_d_00_Container_Weavers_Vector",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1304_Overseer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_15",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "02_Quest_09",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0202_0104_Weavers_Vector_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0202_0104_Weavers_Vector_title",
        "Description": "@0202_0104_Weavers_Vector_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0202_0104_Weavers_Vector_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0202_0104_Weavers_Vector_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0202_0104_Weavers_Vector_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0202_0104_Weavers_Vector_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0210_0102_ReapersLocus",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 35,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0210_0102_d_00_Container_ReapersLocus",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0210_Barkeep",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_Obelisk_11",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "02_Quest_10",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0210_0102_ReapersLocus_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0210_0102_ReapersLocus_title",
        "Description": "@0210_0102_ReapersLocus_quest_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0210_0102_ReapersLocus_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0210_0102_ReapersLocus_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0210_0102_ReapersLocus_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0210_0102_ReapersLocus_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0230_0201_bellyofcorrupted",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0230_0201_d_00_Container_bellyofcorrupted",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0230_Ranger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_16",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0230_0201_bellyofcorrupted_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0230_0201_bellyofcorrupted_title",
        "Description": "@0230_0201_bellyofcorrupted_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0230_0201_bellyofcorrupted_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0230_0201_bellyofcorrupted_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0230_0201_bellyofcorrupted_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0230_0201_bellyofcorrupted_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0230_0202_infernalarmaments",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0230_0202_d_00_Container_infernalarmaments",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0230_Ranger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_17",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "02_Quest_16",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0230_0202_infernalarmaments_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0230_0202_infernalarmaments_title",
        "Description": "@0230_0202_infernalarmaments_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0230_0202_infernalarmaments_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0230_0202_infernalarmaments_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0230_0202_infernalarmaments_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0230_0202_infernalarmaments_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0230_0203_blacksmithbetrayer",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0230_0203_d_00_Container_blacksmithbetrayer",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0230_Ranger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_18",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "02_Quest_17",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0230_0203_blacksmithbetrayer_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0230_0203_blacksmithbetrayer_title",
        "Description": "@0230_0203_blacksmithbetrayer_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0230_0203_blacksmithbetrayer_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0230_0203_blacksmithbetrayer_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0230_0203_blacksmithbetrayer_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0230_0203_blacksmithbetrayer_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0231_0201_locationscout",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 26,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0231_0201_d_00_Container_locationscout",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0231_Painter",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_19",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0231_0201_locationscout_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0231_0201_locationscout_title",
        "Description": "@0231_0201_locationscout_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0231_0201_locationscout_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0231_0201_locationscout_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0231_0201_locationscout_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0231_0201_locationscout_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0231_0202_eyeforreflection",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 27,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0231_0202_d_00_Container_eyeforreflection",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0231_Painter",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_20",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "02_Quest_19",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0231_0202_eyeforreflection_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0231_0202_eyeforreflection_title",
        "Description": "@0231_0202_eyeforreflection_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0231_0202_eyeforreflection_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0231_0202_eyeforreflection_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0231_0202_eyeforreflection_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0231_0202_eyeforreflection_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0231_0203_wolcottsmasterpiece",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 28,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0231_0203_d_00_Container_wolcottsmasterpiece",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0231_Painter",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_21",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "02_Quest_20",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0231_0203_wolcottsmasterpiece_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0231_0203_wolcottsmasterpiece_title",
        "Description": "@0231_0203_wolcottsmasterpiece_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0231_0203_wolcottsmasterpiece_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0231_0203_wolcottsmasterpiece_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0231_0203_wolcottsmasterpiece_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0231_0203_wolcottsmasterpiece_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0232_0201_asimpletea",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0232_0201_d_00_Container_asimpletea",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0232_Naturalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_22",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0232_0201_asimpletea_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0232_0201_asimpletea_title",
        "Description": "@0232_0201_asimpletea_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0232_0201_asimpletea_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0232_0201_asimpletea_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0232_0201_asimpletea_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0232_0201_asimpletea_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0232_0202_hiddensecrets",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0232_0202_d_00_Container_hiddensecrets",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0232_Naturalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_23",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "02_Quest_22",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0232_0202_hiddensecrets_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0232_0202_hiddensecrets_title",
        "Description": "@0232_0202_hiddensecrets_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0232_0202_hiddensecrets_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0232_0202_hiddensecrets_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0232_0202_hiddensecrets_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0232_0202_hiddensecrets_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0232_0203_verdantadelphia",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0232_0203_d_00_Container_verdantadelphia",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0232_Naturalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_24",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "02_Quest_23",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0232_0203_verdantadelphia_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0232_0203_verdantadelphia_title",
        "Description": "@0232_0203_verdantadelphia_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0232_0203_verdantadelphia_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0232_0203_verdantadelphia_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0232_0203_verdantadelphia_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0232_0203_verdantadelphia_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0232_0204_azothtreeachene",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0232_0204_d_00_Container_azothtreeachene",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0232_Naturalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_25",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "02_Quest_24",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0232_0204_azothtreeachene_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0232_0204_azothtreeachene_title",
        "Description": "@0232_0204_azothtreeachene_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0232_0204_azothtreeachene_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0232_0204_azothtreeachene_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0232_0204_azothtreeachene_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0232_0204_azothtreeachene_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0233_0201_bearcohabitation",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0233_0201_d_00_Container_bearcohabitation",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0233_Hunter",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_26",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0233_0201_bearcohabitation_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0233_0201_bearcohabitation_title",
        "Description": "@0233_0201_bearcohabitation_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0233_0201_bearcohabitation_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0233_0201_bearcohabitation_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0233_0201_bearcohabitation_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0233_0201_bearcohabitation_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0233_0202_papabear",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0233_0202_d_00_Container_papabear",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0233_Hunter",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_27",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "02_Quest_26",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0233_0202_papabear_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0233_0202_papabear_title",
        "Description": "@0233_0202_papabear_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0233_0202_papabear_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0233_0202_papabear_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0233_0202_papabear_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0233_0202_papabear_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0234_0201_memoriesofanotherlife",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0234_0201_d_00_Container_memoriesofanotherlife",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0234_Mourner",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_28",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0234_0201_memoriesofanotherlife_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0234_0201_memoriesofanotherlife_title",
        "Description": "@0234_0201_memoriesofanotherlife_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0234_0201_memoriesofanotherlife_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0234_0201_memoriesofanotherlife_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0234_0201_memoriesofanotherlife_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0234_0201_memoriesofanotherlife_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0234_0202_homenomore",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0234_0202_d_00_Container_homenomore",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0234_Mourner",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_29",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "02_Quest_28",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0234_0202_homenomore_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0234_0202_homenomore_title",
        "Description": "@0234_0202_homenomore_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0234_0202_homenomore_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0234_0202_homenomore_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0234_0202_homenomore_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0234_0202_homenomore_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0234_0203_tildeathdouspart",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0234_0203_d_00_Container_tildeathdouspart",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0234_Mourner",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_30",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "02_Quest_29",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0234_0203_tildeathdouspart_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0234_0203_tildeathdouspart_title",
        "Description": "@0234_0203_tildeathdouspart_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0234_0203_tildeathdouspart_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0234_0203_tildeathdouspart_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0234_0203_tildeathdouspart_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0234_0203_tildeathdouspart_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0205_0102_Battles_Embrace_Gear",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 55,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0205_0102_d_00_Container_Battles_Embrace_Gear",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0205_Artificer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_Armor_12",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "02_Quest_10",
        "RequiredLevel": 40,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0205_0102_Battles_Embrace_Gear_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0205_0102_Battles_Embrace_Gear_title",
        "Description": "@0205_0102_Battles_Embrace_Gear_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0205_0102_Battles_Embrace_Gear_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0205_0102_Battles_Embrace_Gear_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0205_0102_Battles_Embrace_Gear_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0205_0102_Battles_Embrace_Gear_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0205_0102_01_Boots",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0205_0102_d_00_Container_01_Boots",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_Armor_12_Boots",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0205_0102_01_Boots_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0205_0102_01_Boots_title",
        "Description": "@0205_0102_01_Boots_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0205_0102_01_Boots_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0205_0102_01_Boots_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0205_0102_01_Boots_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0205_0102_01_Boots_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0205_0102_02_Breastplate",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0205_0102_d_00_Container_02_Breastplate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_Armor_12_Breastplate",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0205_0102_02_Breastplate_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0205_0102_02_Breastplate_title",
        "Description": "@0205_0102_02_Breastplate_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0205_0102_02_Breastplate_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0205_0102_02_Breastplate_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0205_0102_02_Breastplate_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0205_0102_02_Breastplate_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0205_0102_03_Greaves",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0205_0102_d_00_Container_03_Greaves",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_Armor_12_Greaves",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0205_0102_03_Greaves_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0205_0102_03_Greaves_title",
        "Description": "@0205_0102_03_Greaves_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0205_0102_03_Greaves_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0205_0102_03_Greaves_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0205_0102_03_Greaves_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0205_0102_03_Greaves_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0205_0102_04_Gauntlets",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0205_0102_d_00_Container_04_Gauntlets",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_Armor_12_Gauntlets",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0205_0102_04_Gauntlets_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0205_0102_04_Gauntlets_title",
        "Description": "@0205_0102_04_Gauntlets_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0205_0102_04_Gauntlets_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0205_0102_04_Gauntlets_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0205_0102_04_Gauntlets_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0205_0102_04_Gauntlets_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0205_0102_05_Helm",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0205_0102_d_00_Container_05_Helm",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_Armor_12_Helm",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0205_0102_05_Helm_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0205_0102_05_Helm_title",
        "Description": "@0205_0102_05_Helm_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0205_0102_05_Helm_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0205_0102_05_Helm_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0205_0102_05_Helm_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0205_0102_05_Helm_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9804_M_0001_RankUp",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 25,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "9804_M_0001_d_00_Container_RankUp",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "FactionRank_M_0001_RankUp",
        "RequiredFaction": "Marauder",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "98_M_0001_RankUp_success",
        "ProgressionReward": "Marauder 1",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": true,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@98_M_0001_RankUp_title",
        "Description": "@98_M_0001_RankUp_description",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9806_M_0001_RankUp",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 25,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "9806_M_0001_d_00_Container_RankUp",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "FactionRank_M_0001_RankUp",
        "RequiredFaction": "Marauder",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "98_M_0001_RankUp_success",
        "ProgressionReward": "Marauder 1",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": true,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@98_M_0001_RankUp_title",
        "Description": "@98_M_0001_RankUp_description",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9809_M_0001_RankUp",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 25,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "9809_M_0001_d_00_Container_RankUp",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "FactionRank_M_0001_RankUp",
        "RequiredFaction": "Marauder",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "98_M_0001_RankUp_success",
        "ProgressionReward": "Marauder 1",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": true,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@98_M_0001_RankUp_title",
        "Description": "@98_M_0001_RankUp_description",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9812_M_0001_RankUp",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 25,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "9812_M_0001_d_00_Container_RankUp",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "FactionRank_M_0001_RankUp",
        "RequiredFaction": "Marauder",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "98_M_0001_RankUp_success",
        "ProgressionReward": "Marauder 1",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": true,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@98_M_0001_RankUp_title",
        "Description": "@98_M_0001_RankUp_description",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "98_M_01_combatprowess",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 25,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "98_M_01_d_00_Container_combatprowess",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1007_Commander",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "marauders_faction_quest_01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_factionhandoff",
        "RequiredFaction": "Marauder",
        "RequiredLevel": 20,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "98_M_01_combatprowess_success",
        "ProgressionReward": "MarauderTokens 1 1500",
        "ObjectiveReward": "98_M_0102_RankUp",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": true,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@98_M_01_combatprowess_title",
        "Description": "@98_M_01_combatprowess_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@98_M_01_combatprowess_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@98_M_01_combatprowess_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@98_M_01_combatprowess_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@98_M_01_combatprowess_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "98_M_0102_RankUp",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 35,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "98_M_0102_d_00_Container_RankUp",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "FactionRank_M_0102_RankUp",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_factionhandoff",
        "RequiredFaction": "Marauder",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "98_M_0102_RankUp_success",
        "ProgressionReward": "Marauder 2",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": true,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@98_M_0102_RankUp_title",
        "Description": "@98_M_0102_RankUp_description",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "98_M_01b_fenravager",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 35,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "98_M_01b_d_00_Container_fenravager",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1307_Commander",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "marauders_faction_quest_01b",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "marauders_faction_quest_01",
        "RequiredFaction": "Marauder",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "98_M_01b_fenravager_success",
        "ProgressionReward": "MarauderTokens 2 3000",
        "ObjectiveReward": "98_M_0203_RankUp",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": true,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@98_M_01b_fenravager_title",
        "Description": "@98_M_01b_fenravager_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@98_M_01b_fenravager_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@98_M_01b_fenravager_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@98_M_01b_fenravager_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@98_M_01b_fenravager_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "98_M_0203_RankUp",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 49,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "98_M_0203_d_00_Container_RankUp",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "FactionRank_M_0203_RankUp",
        "RequiredFaction": "Marauder",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "98_M_0203_RankUp_success",
        "ProgressionReward": "Marauder 3",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": true,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@98_M_0203_RankUp_title",
        "Description": "@98_M_0203_RankUp_description",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "98_M_02_ultimatewarrior",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 49,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "98_M_02_d_00_Container_ultimatewarrior",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1507_Commander",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "marauders_faction_quest_02",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "marauders_faction_quest_01b",
        "RequiredFaction": "Marauder",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "98_M_02_ultimatewarrior_success",
        "ProgressionReward": "MarauderTokens 3 6000",
        "ObjectiveReward": "98_M_0304_RankUp",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": true,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@98_M_02_ultimatewarrior_title",
        "Description": "@98_M_02_ultimatewarrior_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@98_M_02_ultimatewarrior_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@98_M_02_ultimatewarrior_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@98_M_02_ultimatewarrior_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@98_M_02_ultimatewarrior_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "98_M_0304_RankUp",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "98_M_0304_d_00_Container_RankUp",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "FactionRank_M_0304_RankUp",
        "RequiredFaction": "Marauder",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "98_M_0304_RankUp_success",
        "ProgressionReward": "Marauder 4",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": true,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@98_M_0304_RankUp_title",
        "Description": "@98_M_0304_RankUp_description",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "98_M_03_darkvengeance",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "98_M_03_d_00_Container_darkvengeance",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0807_Commander",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "marauders_faction_quest_03",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "marauders_faction_quest_02",
        "RequiredFaction": "Marauder",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "98_M_03_darkvengeance_success",
        "ProgressionReward": "MarauderTokens 4 12000",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": true,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@98_M_03_darkvengeance_title",
        "Description": "@98_M_03_darkvengeance_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@98_M_03_darkvengeance_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@98_M_03_darkvengeance_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@98_M_03_darkvengeance_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@98_M_03_darkvengeance_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9804_S_0001_RankUp",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 25,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "9804_S_0001_d_00_Container_RankUp",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "FactionRank_S_0001_RankUp",
        "RequiredFaction": "Syndicate",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "98_S_0001_RankUp_success",
        "ProgressionReward": "Syndicate 1",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": true,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@98_S_0001_RankUp_title",
        "Description": "@98_S_0001_RankUp_description",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9806_S_0001_RankUp",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 25,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "9806_S_0001_d_00_Container_RankUp",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "FactionRank_S_0001_RankUp",
        "RequiredFaction": "Syndicate",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "98_S_0001_RankUp_success",
        "ProgressionReward": "Syndicate 1",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": true,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@98_S_0001_RankUp_title",
        "Description": "@98_S_0001_RankUp_description",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9809_S_0001_RankUp",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 25,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "9809_S_0001_d_00_Container_RankUp",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "FactionRank_S_0001_RankUp",
        "RequiredFaction": "Syndicate",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "98_S_0001_RankUp_success",
        "ProgressionReward": "Syndicate 1",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": true,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@98_S_0001_RankUp_title",
        "Description": "@98_S_0001_RankUp_description",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9812_S_0001_RankUp",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 25,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "9812_S_0001_d_00_Container_RankUp",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "FactionRank_S_0001_RankUp",
        "RequiredFaction": "Syndicate",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "98_S_0001_RankUp_success",
        "ProgressionReward": "Syndicate 1",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": true,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@98_S_0001_RankUp_title",
        "Description": "@98_S_0001_RankUp_description",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "98_S_01_theexperiment",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 25,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "98_S_01_d_00_Container_theexperiment",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0208_Alchemist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "syndicate_faction_quest_01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_factionhandoff",
        "RequiredFaction": "Syndicate",
        "RequiredLevel": 20,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "98_S_01_theexperiment_success",
        "ProgressionReward": "SyndicateTokens 1 1500",
        "ObjectiveReward": "98_S_0102_RankUp",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": true,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@98_S_01_theexperiment_title",
        "Description": "@98_S_01_theexperiment_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@98_S_01_theexperiment_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@98_S_01_theexperiment_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@98_S_01_theexperiment_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@98_S_01_theexperiment_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "98_S_0102_RankUp",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 35,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "98_S_0102_d_00_Container_RankUp",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "FactionRank_S_0102_RankUp",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_factionhandoff",
        "RequiredFaction": "Syndicate",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "98_S_0102_RankUp_success",
        "ProgressionReward": "Syndicate 2",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": true,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@98_S_0102_RankUp_title",
        "Description": "@98_S_0102_RankUp_description",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "98_S_01b_fenscholar",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 35,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "98_S_01b_d_00_Container_fenscholar",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1308_Alchemist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "syndicate_faction_quest_01b",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "syndicate_faction_quest_01",
        "RequiredFaction": "Syndicate",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "98_S_01b_fenscholar_success",
        "ProgressionReward": "SyndicateTokens 2 3000",
        "ObjectiveReward": "98_S_0203_RankUp",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": true,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@98_S_01b_fenscholar_title",
        "Description": "@98_S_01b_fenscholar_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@98_S_01b_fenscholar_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@98_S_01b_fenscholar_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@98_S_01b_fenscholar_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@98_S_01b_fenscholar_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "98_S_0203_RankUp",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 49,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "98_S_0203_d_00_Container_RankUp",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "FactionRank_S_0203_RankUp",
        "RequiredFaction": "Syndicate",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "98_S_0203_RankUp_success",
        "ProgressionReward": "Syndicate 3",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": true,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@98_S_0203_RankUp_title",
        "Description": "@98_S_0203_RankUp_description",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "98_S_02_necromanticchemistry",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 49,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "98_S_02_d_00_Container_necromanticchemistry",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1108_Alchemist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "syndicate_faction_quest_02",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "syndicate_faction_quest_01b",
        "RequiredFaction": "Syndicate",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "98_S_02_necromanticchemistry_success",
        "ProgressionReward": "SyndicateTokens 3 6000",
        "ObjectiveReward": "98_S_0304_RankUp",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": true,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@98_S_02_necromanticchemistry_title",
        "Description": "@98_S_02_necromanticchemistry_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@98_S_02_necromanticchemistry_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@98_S_02_necromanticchemistry_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@98_S_02_necromanticchemistry_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@98_S_02_necromanticchemistry_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "98_S_0304_RankUp",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "98_S_0304_d_00_Container_RankUp",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "FactionRank_S_0304_RankUp",
        "RequiredFaction": "Syndicate",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "98_S_0304_RankUp_success",
        "ProgressionReward": "Syndicate 4",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": true,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@98_S_0304_RankUp_title",
        "Description": "@98_S_0304_RankUp_description",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "98_S_03_lostnotlost",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "98_S_03_d_00_Container_lostnotlost",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0508_Alchemist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "syndicate_faction_quest_03",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "syndicate_faction_quest_02",
        "RequiredFaction": "Syndicate",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "98_S_03_lostnotlost_success",
        "ProgressionReward": "SyndicateTokens 4 12000",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": true,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@98_S_03_lostnotlost_title",
        "Description": "@98_S_03_lostnotlost_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@98_S_03_lostnotlost_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@98_S_03_lostnotlost_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@98_S_03_lostnotlost_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@98_S_03_lostnotlost_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9804_C_0001_RankUp",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 25,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "9804_C_0001_d_00_Container_RankUp",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "FactionRank_C_0001_RankUp",
        "RequiredFaction": "Covenant",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "98_C_0001_RankUp_success",
        "ProgressionReward": "Covenant 1",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": true,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@98_C_0001_RankUp_title",
        "Description": "@98_C_0001_RankUp_description",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9806_C_0001_RankUp",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 25,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "9806_C_0001_d_00_Container_RankUp",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "FactionRank_C_0001_RankUp",
        "RequiredFaction": "Covenant",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "98_C_0001_RankUp_success",
        "ProgressionReward": "Covenant 1",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": true,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@98_C_0001_RankUp_title",
        "Description": "@98_C_0001_RankUp_description",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9809_C_0001_RankUp",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 25,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "9809_C_0001_d_00_Container_RankUp",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "FactionRank_C_0001_RankUp",
        "RequiredFaction": "Covenant",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "98_C_0001_RankUp_success",
        "ProgressionReward": "Covenant 1",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": true,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@98_C_0001_RankUp_title",
        "Description": "@98_C_0001_RankUp_description",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9812_C_0001_RankUp",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 25,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "9812_C_0001_d_00_Container_RankUp",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "FactionRank_C_0001_RankUp",
        "RequiredFaction": "Covenant",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "98_C_0001_RankUp_success",
        "ProgressionReward": "Covenant 1",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": true,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@98_C_0001_RankUp_title",
        "Description": "@98_C_0001_RankUp_description",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "98_C_01_theapostate",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 25,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "98_C_01_d_00_Container_theapostate",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0209_Adjudicator",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "covenant_faction_quest_01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_factionhandoff",
        "RequiredFaction": "Covenant",
        "RequiredLevel": 20,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "98_C_01_theapostate_success",
        "ProgressionReward": "CovenantTokens 1 1500",
        "ObjectiveReward": "98_C_0102_RankUp",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": true,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@98_C_01_theapostate_title",
        "Description": "@98_C_01_theapostate_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@98_C_01_theapostate_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@98_C_01_theapostate_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@98_C_01_theapostate_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@98_C_01_theapostate_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "98_C_0102_RankUp",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 35,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "98_C_0102_d_00_Container_RankUp",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "FactionRank_C_0102_RankUp",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_factionhandoff",
        "RequiredFaction": "Covenant",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "98_C_0102_RankUp_success",
        "ProgressionReward": "Covenant 2",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": true,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@98_C_0102_RankUp_title",
        "Description": "@98_C_0102_RankUp_description",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "98_C_01b_fenredemption",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 35,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "98_C_01b_d_00_Container_fenredemption",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1309_Adjudicator",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "covenant_faction_quest_01b",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "covenant_faction_quest_01",
        "RequiredFaction": "Covenant",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "98_C_01b_fenredemption_success",
        "ProgressionReward": "CovenantTokens 2 3000",
        "ObjectiveReward": "98_C_0203_RankUp",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": true,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@98_C_01b_fenredemption_title",
        "Description": "@98_C_01b_fenredemption_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@98_C_01b_fenredemption_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@98_C_01b_fenredemption_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@98_C_01b_fenredemption_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@98_C_01b_fenredemption_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "98_C_0203_RankUp",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 49,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "98_C_0203_d_00_Container_RankUp",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "FactionRank_C_0203_RankUp",
        "RequiredFaction": "Covenant",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "98_C_0203_RankUp_success",
        "ProgressionReward": "Covenant 3",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": true,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@98_C_0203_RankUp_title",
        "Description": "@98_C_0203_RankUp_description",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "98_C_02_soulsalvation",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 49,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "98_C_02_d_00_Container_soulsalvation",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0309_Adjudicator",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "covenant_faction_quest_02",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "covenant_faction_quest_01b",
        "RequiredFaction": "Covenant",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "98_C_02_soulsalvation_success",
        "ProgressionReward": "CovenantTokens 3 6000",
        "ObjectiveReward": "98_C_0304_RankUp",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": true,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@98_C_02_soulsalvation_title",
        "Description": "@98_C_02_soulsalvation_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@98_C_02_soulsalvation_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@98_C_02_soulsalvation_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@98_C_02_soulsalvation_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@98_C_02_soulsalvation_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "98_C_0304_RankUp",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "98_C_0304_d_00_Container_RankUp",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "FactionRank_C_0304_RankUp",
        "RequiredFaction": "Covenant",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "98_C_0304_RankUp_success",
        "ProgressionReward": "Covenant 4",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": true,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@98_C_0304_RankUp_title",
        "Description": "@98_C_0304_RankUp_description",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "98_C_03_thepathtodarkness",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "98_C_03_d_00_Container_thepathtodarkness",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0709_Adjudicator",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "covenant_faction_quest_03",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "covenant_faction_quest_02",
        "RequiredFaction": "Covenant",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "98_C_03_thepathtodarkness_success",
        "ProgressionReward": "CovenantTokens 4 12000",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": true,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@98_C_03_thepathtodarkness_title",
        "Description": "@98_C_03_thepathtodarkness_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@98_C_03_thepathtodarkness_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@98_C_03_thepathtodarkness_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@98_C_03_thepathtodarkness_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@98_C_03_thepathtodarkness_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0204_0104_Executioner_lvl40_Weapon",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0204_0104_d_00_Container_Executioner_lvl40_Weapon",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0204_Overseer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Executioner_00",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "02_Quest_10",
        "RequiredLevel": 40,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0204_0104_Executioner_lvl40_Weapon_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0204_0104_Executioner_title",
        "Description": "@0204_0104_Executioner_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0204_0104_Executioner_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0204_0104_Executioner_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0204_0104_Executioner_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0204_0104_Executioner_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0204_0104_BucaneersPlank_Quest",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0204_0104_BucaneersPlank_Quest_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Executioner_01",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0204_0104_BucaneersPlank_Quest_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0204_0104_BucaneersPlank_Quest_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0204_0104_BucaneersPlank_Quest_description"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0204_0104_HangmansBinding_Quest",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0204_0104_HangmansBinding_Quest_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Executioner_02",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0204_0104_HangmansBinding_Quest_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0204_0104_HangmansBinding_Quest_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0204_0104_HangmansBinding_Quest_description"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0204_0104_BladeBrute_Quest",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0204_0104_BladeBrute_Quest_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Executioner_03",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0204_0104_BladeBrute_Quest_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0204_0104_BladeBrute_Quest_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0204_0104_BladeBrute_Quest_description"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0204_0104_InfernalCoagulant_Quest",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0204_0104_InfernalCoagulant_Quest_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Executioner_04",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0204_0104_InfernalCoagulant_Quest_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0204_0104_InfernalCoagulant_Quest_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0204_0104_InfernalCoagulant_Quest_description"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0203_0103_Hope_Manifest_lvl40_Weapon",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0203_0103_d_00_Container_Hope_Manifest_lvl40_Weapon",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0203_Survivalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_HopeManifest_00",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "02_Quest_10",
        "RequiredLevel": 40,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0203_0103_Hope_Manifest_lvl40_Weapon_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0203_0103_Hope_Manifest_title",
        "Description": "@0203_0103_Hope_Manifest_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0203_0103_Hope_Manifest_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0203_0103_Hope_Manifest_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0203_0103_Hope_Manifest_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0203_0103_Hope_Manifest_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0203_0103_MendersCloth_Quest",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0203_0103_MendersCloth_Quest_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_HopeManifest_01",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0203_0103_MendersCloth_Quest_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0203_0103_MendersCloth_Quest_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0203_0103_MendersCloth_Quest_description"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0203_0103_SoothsayerSalve_Quest",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0203_0103_SoothsayerSalve_Quest_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_HopeManifest_02",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0203_0103_SoothsayerSalve_Quest_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0203_0103_SoothsayerSalve_Quest_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0203_0103_SoothsayerSalve_Quest_description"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0203_0103_MercysBreath_Quest",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0203_0103_MercysBreath_Quest_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_HopeManifest_03",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0203_0103_MercysBreath_Quest_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0203_0103_MercysBreath_Quest_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0203_0103_MercysBreath_Quest_description"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0203_0103_HopeCatalyst_Quest",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0203_0103_HopeCatalyst_Quest_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_HopeManifest_04",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0203_0103_HopeCatalyst_Quest_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0203_0103_HopeCatalyst_Quest_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0203_0103_HopeCatalyst_Quest_description"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_02_PVP_Spy_Marauder_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_02_PVP_Spy_Marauder_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_02_PVP_Poach_Marauder_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_02_PVP_Poach_Marauder_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_02_PVP_Control_Marauder_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_02_PVP_Control_Marauder_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_02_PVP_Spy_Syndicate_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_02_PVP_Spy_Syndicate_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_02_PVP_Poach_Syndicate_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_02_PVP_Poach_Syndicate_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_02_PVP_Control_Syndicate_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_02_PVP_Control_Syndicate_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_02_PVP_Spy_Covenant_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_02_PVP_Spy_Covenant_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_02_PVP_Poach_Covenant_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_02_PVP_Poach_Covenant_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_02_PVP_Control_Covenant_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_02_PVP_Control_Covenant_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0201_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0201_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0202_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0202_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0203_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0203_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0204_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0204_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0205_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0205_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0206_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0206_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0207_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0207_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0208_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0208_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0209_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0209_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0210_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0210_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0201_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0201_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0202_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0202_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0203_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0203_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0204_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0204_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0205_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0205_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0206_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0206_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0207_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0207_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0208_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0208_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0209_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0209_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0210_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0210_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0201_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0201_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0202_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0202_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0203_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0203_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0204_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0204_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0205_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0205_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0206_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0206_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0207_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0207_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0208_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0208_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0209_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0209_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0210_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0210_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0261_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0261_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0262_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0262_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0263_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0263_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0264_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0264_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0265_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0265_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0266_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0266_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0267_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0267_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0268_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0268_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0269_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0269_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0270_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0270_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0261_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0261_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0262_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0262_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0263_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0263_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0264_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0264_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0265_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0265_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0266_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0266_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0267_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0267_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0268_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0268_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0269_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0269_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0270_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0270_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0261_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0261_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0262_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0262_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0263_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0263_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0264_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0264_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0265_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0265_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0266_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0266_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0267_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0267_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0268_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0268_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0269_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0269_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0270_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0270_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_02_H_01_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_02_H_01_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_02_H_02_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_02_H_02_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_02_H_03_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_02_H_03_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    }
]